http://www.nameplatedepot.com/terms_privacy.asp

MENU
more than a gift, a personal touch!
Privacy Policy
NamePlateDepot is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you a powerful and safe consumer experience. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") outlines how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.nameplatedepot.com (the “Site”). We do not guarantee the accuracy of any translated versions of this Policy. To the extent any translated versions of this Policy conflict with the English language version, the English language version of this Policy shall control.
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
NamePlateDepot
may collect personally identifiable information from you in various ways. NamePlateDepot
may use the following sources:
by signing up to mailing lists at NamePlateDepot
websites;
from an online, retail, abandon cart or telephone purchase;
when you enter an NamePlateDepot
sponsored sweepstakes or giveaway;
when you sign up for an NamePlateDepot
loyalty program;
from a third party with your consent (e.g., your bank);
from our information technology systems (e.g., automated monitoring of our websites); and
when contacting NamePlateDepot
or visiting NamePlateDepot
websites.
Personally identifiable information refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. It includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, email address, postal address, and social networking information. The collected information falls into the following categories:
identifiers (e.g., name, alias, postal address, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or similar identifiers);
information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with a particular individual (e.g., credit card number, telephone number, address, or similar information);
characteristics of protected classifications under federal law;
commercial information (e.g., records regarding goods purchased, or other purchasing histories or tendencies);
internet or other electronic network activity (e.g., browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an online site or application, or similar information);
geo-location data;
audio, electronic, or similar information; and
information drawn from any of the above to create a consumer profile that includes characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behaviors, or similar information.
NamePlateDepot
may also collect certain non-identifying information, or aggregate information, such as anonymous demographic information including zip codes, dates of birth, customer preferences, information about customer computer hardware and software, as well as information about the links and pages that users access within an NamePlateDepot
website. Certain non-identifying information may be considered personally identifiable information if combined with other information which may enable you to be identified (such as a zip code with a street address); however, the same information when taken alone or combined with other non-identifying information, will be considered non-identifying information.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through NamePlateDepot
operated public message boards or reviews, such information may be collected and used by others.
Occasionally NamePlateDepot
will offer links to third party websites. NamePlateDepot
encourages you to review the privacy policies of websites you choose to link to from NamePlateDepot
websites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. NamePlateDepot
is not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on non-NamePlateDepot
websites.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
NamePlateDepot
may store and use your personally identifiable information for (i) product or service fulfillment, (ii) voluntary marketing, promotional, and advertising purposes, such as to inform you of products or services available from NamePlateDepot , (iii) internal operations, such as improving your customer experience, this includes auditing current interactions and optimizing user experience, (iv) detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive activity, and taking all necessary and appropriate steps to mitigate current and future risk; (v) debugging and repairing internal information technology as necessary; (vi) undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration; and (vii) to share with trusted third party service providers to help NamePlateDepot
perform activities to improve your customer experience with your consent ("Business Purposes"). Third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information beyond providing services to NamePlateDepot
and are required to maintain the information's confidentiality and privacy. The categories of the third parties we share personally identifiable information with follow:
credit card processors and other companies that help facilitate your transactions;
companies that provide statistical analysis of your interactions with us;
companies that provide customer support or arrange for deliveries;
companies that helps in personalizing your product;
companies that provide advertising and digital content;
companies that power our online store e.g. Volusion; see their privacy policy here https://www.volusion.com/privacy-policy
companies that support e-commerce marketing efforts; and
The following categories of information are shared for Business Purposes:
identifiers (e.g., name, alias, postal address, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or similar identifiers);
information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with a particular individual (e.g., credit card number, telephone number, address, or similar information);
characteristics of protected classifications under federal law;
commercial information (e.g., records regarding goods purchased, or other purchasing histories or tendencies);
internet or other electronic network activity (e.g., browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an online site or application, or similar information);
geolocation data;
audio, electronic, or similar information; and
information drawn from any of the above to create a consumer profile that includes characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behaviors, or similar information.
NamePlateDepot
does not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties. NamePlateDepot
may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, without your consent, your personally identifiable information would not be transferred to the third party
NamePlateDepot
is not limited in our use of aggregate information that does not permit direct association with any specific individual, such as the number of users of our services, the geographic distribution of our users, the amount of information located or removed, etc. For example, NamePlateDepot
may use aggregate information concerning which links and pages users access within an NamePlateDepot
website for many reasons including to determine which NamePlateDepot
products and services are the most popular. This data may be used to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
NamePlateDepot
will disclose your personally identifiable information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with legal process served; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NamePlateDepot ; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of and NamePlateDepot
website or the public.
Additionally, NamePlateDepot
may disclose personally identifiable information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you).
As with any other business, NamePlateDepot
may merge with or be purchased by another company. If NamePlateDepot
is acquired, the company that acquires us would have access to the information maintained by us, including personally identifiable information, but would continue to be bound by this Policy unless and until it is amended.
Security Protections for your Information
NamePlateDepot
takes the security of your personally identifiable information very seriously. NamePlateDepot
uses reasonable administrative, physical, and technical safeguards to secure the personally identifiable information you share with us. Despite these safeguards and our additional efforts to secure your information, NamePlateDepot
cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security, and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your personally identifiable information.
The security of your NamePlateDepot
website account relies on your protection of your user profile information. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your user profile information, including your password and for all activities that occur under your account. You may not share your password with anyone. We will never ask you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an email, though we may ask you to enter this type of information on an NamePlateDepot
website.
Any email or other communication purporting to be from one of our websites requesting your password or asking you to provide sensitive account information via email, should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to us immediately by emailing NamePlateDepot info [at] nameplatedepot [dot] com. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account and report it immediately by emailing info [at] nameplatedepot [dot] com.
Use of Cookies or Similar Technology
NamePlateDepot
websites work with a first party cookie that collects anonymous traffic data, a form of aggregate information. "Cookies" are simple text files stored on your computer for use by a browser. NamePlateDepot
may use "cookies" to assist in data collection and to track visitor website usage and trends to help us better serve you. If you reject cookies, you will still be able to view our websites, but your ability to use some areas of the websites will be limited. Some of our business partners and publishers (e.g., analytical tracking software providers) use cookies and tracking technologies on our websites. We have no access to or control over these third party cookies or tracking technologies. This Policy covers the use of cookies on our websites by us only and does not cover the use of cookies or tracking technologies by any such business partner.
We may also use cookies, pixels, beacons, or other web tracking technologies to track the amount of time spent on our websites or social media and whether certain content, such as a video, was viewed. We may work with a trusted third party to collect and process this information for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy.
When you visit NamePlateDepot's website, NamePlateDepot
automatically collects the name of the website you visited from (called the "referring page") and the name of the website you chose to visit immediately after ours (called the "exit page"), and information about other websites you have recently visited. This information is used to improve our website, but we cannot identify you from any information we receive from cookies. Some browsers have a "do not track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, and our websites are not currently set up to respond to those signals for tracking on our websites.
Participation in Interest-Based Advertising
NamePlateDepot
may also participate in interest-based advertising using similar technology. Therefore, you may see advertising on our websites tailored to how you browse or shop, or you may see advertising for NamePlateDepot
and its properties on other websites based on your browsing behavior across websites. Some websites where we may advertise belong to ad networks that use your web browsing history to choose which ads to display on their network websites; these ads include advertising for NamePlateDepot
and its websites. Other websites where you see our ads, such as Facebook, may use interest preferences that you have chosen on those sites, as well as registration and other information about you, to choose which ads to display to you. Some internet browsers, websites such as Facebook and mobile devices offer opt-outs for interest-based advertising. Please refer to the website that you are visiting, your browser, or your device settings for additional information.
You can opt-out of receiving interest-based ads from third parties who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and DAA website (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
Your can also opt-out of targeted advertising by visiting below pages
-FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
-GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
-BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Opt-Out/Unsubscribe
You can opt-out or unsubscribe from receiving email correspondence from NamePlateDepot
at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button in email received or by following the instructions contained in any email received. It may take time to process opt-out requests, so you may receive emails from NamePlateDepot
after your opt-out request.
Children's Privacy
NamePlateDepot's websites are not targeted for use by children under the age of 18 and
does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children in connection with the features of our websites without the consent of a parent or guardian. NamePlateDepot
requests that all visitors under 18 to our websites not disclose or provide any personally identifiable information. Upon notification that a child under 18 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete the child's personally identifiable information from our records.
Please note that we may not delete your personal information if it is necessary to:
-complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected;
-provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us;
-detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive activity, and take all necessary and appropriate steps to mitigate current and future risk;
Users Outside the Canada
NamePlateDepot
is headquartered in the Canada. If you are visiting our websites from another country, the laws governing our website's collection and use of personally identifiable information may be different from the laws of your country. If you decide to visit our website, or share your personally identifiable information with NamePlateDepot, you are agreeing to be governed by the laws of the Canada, and you are expressly consenting to the transfer of your data to Canada.
Changes to this Statement/
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by online form located at https://www.nameplatedepot.com/Articles.asp?ID=256
Effective as of January 1, 2020
